<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="77321" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Super Fast Building And Leveling" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Quickly complete building construction and increase building levels." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
# Super Fast Building And Leveling (Previously Infinite Demand)

This mod will force buildings to be built almost instantly.
Additionally, you can enable fast leveling to increase their levels quicker.

## Notice
This mod does not fill houses with citizens.
It will cause rapid building, but they will become abandoned if no one moves in. 
I recommend using the Abandoned Building Remover Mod in addition to this one to help deal with the abandoned buildings.

## Features
### Super Fast Building
The game will almost instantly build all zoned property types, regardless of current demand.

### Fast Leveling
This option is disabled by default. Enable this to increase the level of the buildings at a faster rate.
Enabling this setting may cause the game to stutter depending on your city's size.

### Reset Settings
Use the reset button to reset all of the mods settings to default. 

## How It Works
This mod utilizes the Super Fast Building and Fast Leveling debug options ordinarily available in developer mode.
Using Harmony, they are enabled by patching the game's code.

## Legacy Features (Infinite Demand)

This mod also allows you to control demand for each zone type.
Depending on your simulation speed, the demand sliders may take a while to increase.
I could never completely understand how the demand system works and expand on this part of the mod. 
It fills the demand bars and impacts the demand system on a relatively small level.
I've decided to leave this in the mod for now and rename it to better represent it's main features. 
By disabling it, the game's original demand is restored.

### Sliders For Each Property Type
You can adjust the demand for each property type (Residential, Commercial, Office, and Industrial) individually on a scale of 0-100. 

### Disable Demand Override For Each Property Type
You can turn off the override for each property type (Residential, Commercial, Office, and Industrial) and allow the game to calculate the demand as normal. 

## Other Information

### Compatibility  and Removal
You can remove the mod at any time, and your save games should not be affected; the normal demand levels will be restored as determined by the game.
This mod should not have any compatibility issues with other mods.

### Languages
To use languages other than English, please utilize I18n Everywhere.
Thank you to Baka-gourd and the team of translators for helping make mods more accessible!

## Contact
Please use the discussion forum if you have any questions.
Alternatively, join the Cities Skylines: Modding Discord server for more direct communication.

	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/sfbal1.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/sfbal2.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/sfbal3.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/sfbal4.png" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/super-fast-building-and-leveling-previously-infinite-demand.1655966/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="2.0" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.1.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="75426" DisplayName="I18n EveryWhere" Version="1.1.0-snapshot20240411" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog>
**v2.0**
- Update for compatibility with patch 1.1.10f1
- Renamed mod from Infinite Demand to Super Fast Building And Leveling
- Moved demand override features to Legacy Tab in settings
- Cleaned up the Settings Menu

	</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/RealTitanGod/SuperFastBuildingAndLeveling" />
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />
</Publish>
