<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="77321" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Infinite Demand" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Super fast building and unlimited demand." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
# Infinite Demand
This mod will force buildings to be built almost instantly.
Additionally, you can enable fast leveling to increase their levels quicker.

This mod also allows you to adjust building demand to your desired level.
Depending on your simulation speed, the demand sliders may take a while to increase.
Using the sliders instead of Ultimate Demand may work less efficiently. 

## Notice
This mod does not fill houses with citizens.
It will cause rapid building, but they will become abandoned if no one moves in. 
I recommend using the Abandoned Building Remover Mod in addition to this one to help deal with the abandoned buildings.

## Features
### Super Fast Build and Ultimate Demand
The game will build all property types almost instantly. All other demand settings are ignored when this is enabled.

### Fast Leveling
Enable this to increase the level of the buildings at a faster rate.

### Sliders For Each Property Type
You can adjust the demand for each property type (Residential, Commerical, Office, and Industrial) individually on a scale of 0-100. 

### Disable Demand Override For Each Property Type
You turn off the override for each property type (Residential, Commerical, Office, and Industrial) and allow the game to calculate the demand as normal. 

### Reset Settings
Use the reset button to reset all of the mods settings to default. 

### Compatability and Removal
You can remove the mod at any time, and your save games should not be affected; the normal demand levels will be restored as determined by the game.
This mod should not have any compatibility issues with other mods.

### Languages
For loading languages other than English please utilize I18n Everywhere.
Thank you to Baka-gourd and the team of translators helping make mods more accessible!

## Contact
Please use the discussion forum if you have any questions.

	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/infinitedemand1.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/infinitedemand2.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/infinitedemand3.png" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/infinite-demand-mod.1655966/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.1.2" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.1.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="75426" DisplayName="I18n EveryWhere" Version="1.1.0-snapshot20240411" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog>
**v1.1.2**
- Fixed Fast Leveling causing the simulation to stutter in game update 1.1.6f1

	</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/RealTitanGod/InfiniteDemand" />
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />
</Publish>
